sitetalkcashback.com 2016-11-04

# SiteTalkCashBack Official Site - Global #1 CashBack Shopping Place.

Privacy Policy  
---  
  
Rest assured that privacy, security and integrity are first and foremost at SiteTalk Community Inc (hereinafter called SiteTalk)  
  
What data we collect and why  
  
Our vision is to maximize the shopping experience and possibility to earn rewards for all SiteTalk Members, plus to provide as many member benefits as possible. The key way in which SiteTalk provides value is to share with members the commissions we receive from our affiliated stores. The information we collect (name, email address, and sometimes physical address, PayPal account) is used to track and send the CashBack payments members earn.

Additionally, we may use information on the stores you visit or the offers you view on www.sitetalkcashback.com to select special offers that will be relevant to you. Except at an aggregate level, however, we do not share that information with our store partners or other third parties.

Finally, SiteTalk collects data on the devices that access or attempt to access our websites. This device data is used in conjunction with a third party security partner to identify and prevent fraudulent activity and does not include personally identifiable information.  
  
Who sees your personal information?  
  
We will share your personal information with third parties only in the ways that are described in this privacy notice. We do not sell or offer your personal information to third parties.

Only a very limited number of our employees ever have access to your personal information. We may use third-party contractors or vendors to help us provide some of our services. If we need to disclose personal information for them to provide the services, it is with the requirement that the information will be kept confidential and used only to provide those services. In addition, our affiliates, subsidiaries, service providers, and other entities may collect personal information about your browsing habits over time and across different Web sites when you use our website.

We reserve the right to disclose your personal information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on us or to protect us and our members from losses.

While browsers allow you to disable the usage of cookies, we do not change our practices in response to a "Do Not Track" signal in the http header from your browser or mobile application. Read more about the cookie policy below.

If we (or one of our affiliated companies) are involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of our assets, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice this website of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information.  
  
How we keep your information secure  
  
The security of your personal information is important to SiteTalk. SiteTalk.com uses a secure, encrypted connection (called an SSL connection) on all pages where you access or transmit personal information.  
  
Your privacy with SiteTalk  
  
SiteTalk will never ask for your username, password or any other personal information in an unsolicited phone call, email or letter. Further, any contact with SiteTalk customer service in which personal information is exchanged with a customer service representative will be used only for the purpose of satisfying your request. Any personal information you provide will not be recorded or used for any reason beyond that of the stated request.

If you choose to use our referral program to tell a friend, invite a friend or recommend a store on our site, we will ask you for your friend's name and email address. We will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the site.

SiteTalk stores this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email and tracking the success of our referral program. Your friend may contact us using the contact form on our website to request that we remove this information from our database.

If we change our privacy policy, we will post a change notice to this privacy statement and other appropriate places. We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it regularly. If we make changes to this policy, we will notify you, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page.  
  
Your privacy with our stores and advertisers  
  
SiteTalk does not record personal information passed from our members to affiliated stores. Order information, including order numbers and amounts, may be available to SiteTalk, the store, or third party affiliate program management companies for accurate tracking purposes, but his information will not be released by SiteTalk to other parties.  
SiteTalk contains links to various other sites. Each of these sites has a privacy policy that may differ from that of SiteTalk. If you wish to receive special offers directly from a store, neither this privacy policy nor our opt-out policy applies to those communications. Instead, please refer to the relevant store's privacy and opt-out policy.  
  
Our policies on email  
  
SiteTalk sends two types of email to members: customer service emails required maintaining the SiteTalk program (like CashBack, credits & payment notifications); and promotional emails featuring especially good offers. You may choose not to receive promotional emails at any time from SiteTalk CashBack by changing the setting in your account.

SiteTalk does not support spamming by our members and we explicitly prohibit it in our Terms and Conditions. If you would like to report an incident of spamming using our tell-a-friend capability, please [contact us.](http://www.sitetalkcashback.com/in-en/contact-us). We will investigate and take suitable action.  
  
Cookies  
What are cookies?  
  
This website uses cookies to collect information. Cookies are small data files which are placed on your computer or other mobile or handheld device (such as smart 'phones or 'tablets') as you browse this website. They are used to 'remember' when your computer or device accesses this website. The cookies are essential to the effective operation of our website and to enable to you to earn rewards and using our add-on online. Cookies are also used to tailor the products and services offered and advertised to our customers, both on this website and elsewhere.  
  
Information collected  
  
Some cookies collect information about browsing and purchasing behavior by people who access this website via the same computer or device. This includes information about pages viewed and the customer journey around a website. We do not, however, use cookies to collect or record information on users' name, address or other contact details.  
  
Who sets the cookies?  
  
The cookies stored on your computer or other device when you access this website are set by SiteTalk and other third parties. Some cookies are set by or on behalf of SiteTalk and are necessary to enable customers to a make earn rewards on our website.

Cookies may also be set by third parties who participate with us in affiliate marketing or advertising marketing programs.   
  
What are cookies used for?  
  
The main purposes for which cookies are used are:

1\. For technical purposes essential to effective operation of website, particularly in relation to click outs from our site to stores.

2\. To drive SiteTalk marketing.

3\. To enable SiteTalk to collect information about the browsing habits and activities of our customers, including monitoring the success of visited stores that earn CashBack rewards.

4\. To enable SiteTalk meet its contractual obligations to make payments to customers that have earned CashBack rewards.  
  
How do I disable cookies?  
  
If you want to disable cookies you need to change your website browser settings to reject cookies. How to do this will depend on the browser you use and we provide further detail below on how to disable cookies for the most popular browsers:

For Microsoft Internet Explorer:  
1\. Choose the menu "tools" then "Internet Options"  
2\. Click on the "privacy" tab  
3\. Select the setting the appropriate setting

For Mozilla firefox:  
1\. Choose the menu "tools" then "Options"  
2\. Click on the icon "privacy"  
3\. Find the menu "cookie" and select the relevant options

For Opera 6.0 and further:  
1\. Choose the menu Files"> "Preferences"  
2\. Privacy

For Google Chrome:  
1\. Choose the menu Chrome"> "Preferences"  
2\. Click on "advanced settings"  
3\. Click on "privacy" and then "content settings" to change cookies  
  
What happens if I disable cookies?  
  
This depends on which cookies you disable, but in general the site may not operate properly if cookies are switched off. Disabling all cookies in your browser will not enable you to get any rewards from our site when visiting any shop displayed regardless if you have the add-on installed and enabled  
  
Your choices and responsibilities  
  
Periodically we may send you emails on new features or special offers. It is the member's responsibility to update and maintain accurate contact information in their account. You can make changes by visiting your [account page](https://www.sitetalkcashback.com/in-en/front/profile_detail/) and entering corrections. Email and street addresses that are entered into a member's personal profile page are the addresses that may be used for all contact including for sending you cash back payments. SiteTalk is not responsible for payments sent to incorrect information provided by you.

We will post all changes to this Privacy Agreement here at our site. You are responsible for checking periodically on policy updates.

Please feel free to contact us if you have any questions about our Privacy Policy and Cookie Policy or our information practices.

In the event of any conflict between the English and other language versions, the English version shall prevail.

Effective Date: January 20th 2015
